Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Leo Deaner collection 1902-2006 IBT0022
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- James P. Hoffa, 1991-2008; Series 18; 1.5 Linear Feet
  - Restructuring and Finances, 2002-2008; Series 19; .5 Linear Feet
    - Restructuring - Organizational Chart, 2005 (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Restructuring Proposal, August 2005 (Box 164, Folder 12)
    - Restructuring - Research Department, Restructured to Economics and Contracts, November 2005; Series 18 (Box 164, Folder 13)
    - Restructuring - Strategic Research and Campaigns, November 2005 (Box 164, Folder 14)
    - Restructuring - Education Department, Restructured to IBT Department of Training and Development, 2005-2006 (Box 164, Folder 15)
    - Restructuring - Government Affairs, January 2007 (Box 164, Folder 16)
  - 'Where is Hoffa Driving the Teamsters?' The Nation, Vol 271, No. 4, July 2000; Series 18 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - "The Discreet Charm of Hoffa Jr.", article from Exchange, September 2000; Series 18 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - 'A Just Response,' The Nation, Vol 273, No. 10, October 2001; Series 18 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - 'Teamsters Celebrate Black History Month,' Teamster Magazine, Vol. 103, No. 1, February 2006; Series 18 (Box 165, Folder 12)